Music
Yes, we've finished rehearsal.
Well, we've finished rehearsal, and our ear monitors were in perfect shape today.
Our ear monitors were in perfect shape, and the air was so full of air, and the audience was so spacious that I was really looking forward to the show.
I was really looking forward to the show.
So, today we are going to Tochigi, Izu-kara-chan's hometown, for the first time.
I'm looking forward to it!
My long awaited concert is here today!
Tochigi, Tochigi, Tochigi... Yay! It's my first time here!
I couldn't sleep on the bus today because the game was on.
That's rare. But I did sleep in the second half.
The nice thing about helping people is that we have many names you can understand.
Sure, it's called Nikko, or Nikko, or Fuller Park, or Ashikaga Fuller Park.
So there's a place where everyone knows it.
It's hard to know... but there's a lot of stuff here.
Great name!
Good evening. Good evening.
Good evening. How are you feeling? I'm feeling a little hungry.
No, I know. I haven't eaten anything. You haven't eaten anything?
I haven't eaten anything.
Then go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Thank you very much.
Do you have anything to say?
I love you, sir.
What do you love about it?
You have taught me the beauty of entertainment.
See you in the next video.
Hello, hello, hello, how are you feeling today?
What do you like about her?
Mr. Assi.
I like your hair, Mr. Assi, it's very cool.
Mr. Assy's hair is ash, right?
I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
What are you doing now?
I see you're wearing blush.
This one's nice, too.
May I? Thank you very much.
You want to go strawberry? On the cheeks.
More like orange.
How are you feeling today?
Salmon.
That's how you feel.
Well, good luck with your salmon.
It's salmon.
No, no, no, no, no!
Isshin-kun's here, too.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
How are you feeling today?
Salmon.
This is not good.
Bye-bye, Ichichan.
What'll you have next?
Salmon roe.
Salmon roe sounds good.
I hate salmon roe.
I went to the roadside station when I came here.
They were selling strawberries.
I said I wanted strawberries.
I said, "I'm sure you'll get some at the caterer's today.
I'm sure they'll be served at the catering today.
I was so excited!
I hope you'll be able to eat strawberries.
This is Annie.
She's finished with her makeup.
Now I'm going to put on my lipstick.
This is my new lip.
Pop-pop-pop!
Huh?
Pop-pop-pop.
Pop-pop-pop!
I can say strawberry!
It has strawberries in it!
Oh, man, it's hot! It's really hot!
Are the strawberries really delicious?
You gave me back the strawberries too, didn't you?
Strawberries.
They had them in America.
They're good!
They're so good!
They're good, aren't they?
They're amazing!
Hi, I'm Runo Iizuka from Tochigi. Today is my first live performance in my hometown.
It's delicious! Have you been introduced to bento?
What a surprise!
There's a whole strawberry in it! And look at this!
And look at this! It's yakisoba with potatoes!
I can't stand it if it doesn't have potatoes!
And look at this.
We are going to sing a song of the people of Tochigi.
I used to sing this song every morning in elementary school.
I never thought that the day would come when I would be singing it with everyone at One Love One Heart.
I can't imagine what I was like in elementary school.
Which one of you is me?
Carrots, you've got to be kidding me!
There were a lot of carrots.
I hate the way you eat them!
I feel sorry for strawberries.
How do you like it? Is it good?
I'll eat you too.
What do you think?
They're enjoying the strawberries.
Some people are saying, "Let's eat strawberries, too.
I'd rather eat Ajak strawberries.
Ajak.
One bite and it's amazing.
Oh, how cute!
We're practicing the song now. Isn't it interesting?
It's really interesting to see people who are not Tochigi residents singing this One Love One Heart song.
And they're singing about their hometowns.
Today, we all gathered in the morning and came here by bus, so we were up early.
It's kind of amazing, I'm in the waiting room all the time, so it's kind of strange.
I'm wondering if I'm really in Tochigi, or Tokyo, or Nagano Prefecture, or something.
But I had rehearsed and heard the prefectural anthem, and when I sang it again, I was surprised that I could sing it,
It was a lot of fun.
I was so moved that I almost feel like a Tochigi resident now.
What is your motivation? My mind is.
So today, we are going to perform with earphones for the first time. So I'm looking forward to it.
So I'm a little excited about it, so I'm looking forward to it.
I have performed with rented earphones before, but it was totally different, and I was really excited.
So I'm really looking forward to the show.
I'm looking forward to the show.
Well, this is not the choreography for the new song.
Well, when we recorded the song, I had time to get bored.
Well, I had 4:00 after this.
I was bored the whole time. Oh, well, let's stick to it a little bit more, a little bit.
I always, I don't know how to say it.
I always decorated with simple things, so I decided to be a little more particular about it.
I want to eat number 13.
Oh, 31! I said, "Oh, 31!
I wasn't really planning to write 31, but I said, "I want to do 31.
I said, "I want to do 31," and I wrote it, and then I spent two hours on MERU, and I worked hard.
It was the only thing I did that I didn't give up on until the end.
One of them is the 31 countdown.
Please give me a compliment.
It's my favorite.
One more time, one more time. Take it from the top, from the top.
What's different?
Oh, my God!
How many more mouths are there?
Slanted mouth.
Just one.
Change it? This one.
Oh, shit.
Okay, passive mouth.
Height.
There's a lot of rusks here.
Rena got them from her mom.
Here's Renateur.
Oh my God!
Thank you, Mom.
Thank you, Mom!
I met your mother.
My sister was here too.
Thank you, sister.
And next year, on January 8th, we'll be holding S4 Montbrand Sky Triffet in all of our locations.
Oh, I made a mistake.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake.
Oh, not yet.
Then let me out.
Teeves Evolution.
You Arch Show
Teebs Original.
Now, now, now.
It's finally going live, and it's really
I'd like to make all the people
I want to make everyone in the city fall in love with me!
one love one heart
What the heck! What the heck!
How's Tochigi? The script dumplings are delicious.
Have you had gyoza?
Scripted dumplings are in the bento box.
I looked at the script, and in the bento box from the food stand...
I found scripted fried gyoza.
The script has a lot of chives.
Yeah, with chives...
I looked up "script with more chives".
Three cars are at the top of the list.
Top.
Top?
First place.
Top of the line, I hear.
That means we're top.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
Yes, sir.
Second in the nation.
We were number two. Number one.
Second in the nation. Chives.
The dumplings were so chivey and delicious.
Thank you very much.
♪ I have bred hatred ♪
Dazai
It's the earpiece debut, Love Ann.
Our own earpiece.
They're good ones.
Janie is
Please
Please, please, please.
Let's go for it.
This is our first live performance as Warabowa Heart in Tochigi Prefecture.
I'm sure there are many who have never seen us before.
Let's leave our mark. This is our foundation.
Let's get fired up!
We are Warabowa Heart
Fresh!
Thank you for listening.
Thank you for waiting.
Thank you very much
thank you for your hard work
thank you very much
Chigimi Live Iitokotochigi has ended!
And to our surprise, we sold out the hand-sold tickets!
Noisy order!
We did our best at hand-selling!
Many people received our flyers!
All the members were so excited to receive the flyers
We were so happy to see the warmth of Tochigi people.
Tochigi is the best!
It warmed our hearts.
I think everyone loves Tochigi now!
I love Tochigi!
The dumplings are delicious!
I used to think Tochigi was all about strawberries
People are the best!
Tochigi is the best!
Thank you so much!
Thank you so much. I'm so happy.
I'll be back soon.
Soon. Soon.
Coming soon. Thank you very much.
Let's go, let's go, let's go.